[{"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 13, "question": "Does that mean I'm lying to you?", "qSentId": 12}, {"answer": "Well, I'll tell you.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 25, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 24}, {"answer": "Well, I'm not nearly as interesting as you just described.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "Robert, how are you?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "You do.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "Do I look like that?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "And I've been roaming around the country and doing -- what the hell have I been doing?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "I had a Facebook.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "Communicate with them through Facebook and stuff, right?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "How much of it -- I mean you've ridden this extraordinary book.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "Did I really live this thing?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "I -- OK, I'll get serious for just a minute.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "Well, because she was the woman that was doing these at the time, right?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "Well, I'll tell you.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "I don't blame anybody.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "How much do you blame your parents?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "LAKE: Never.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "Did they ever tell you that they loved you, your parents?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "Oh, I think that if I came from a different family, I would have been a very different person.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "But although you don't necessarily blame them because of your belief in God, how much do you think did it damage your character, damage your personality, make you a damaged person?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 210, "question": "Are you capable of love?", "qSentId": 209}, {"answer": "Let's -- let's take a short break, Robert.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "How could you not love a God that kept you in the womb when you were supposed to be dead out of the womb?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "Could I just say one word about this?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "What your relationship was like with her before she died.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "Now what would you like to hear?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "Did you love her, though?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "Nobody ever knows -- everything and I -- particularly a person like Bonnie.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "Did you know everything about her?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "I think she was a con artist, yes.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "Was she a con artist?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "Do you believe that --", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "Rewind?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "Does that mean I'm lying to you?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "What did you think?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "I don't care about that.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "I'm saying I've met you for, what, 20 minutes?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "Because you just insulted me.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "Why are you being so defensive?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "I said I'm going to ask you --", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "What the hell is the difference?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "-- well documented -- I heard what you said.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "Did you hear what I said?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "You mean physically faithful?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "I don't represent anybody.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "Do you represent some of those people?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "ORGAN: Tell me.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "Do you know why I was arrested?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "No, I don't.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "You got any idea why, why I was under arrest for four years and he was under arrest for an hour, Mr. Research?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "I told you why.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "Why were you found liable?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "I would have been -- I -- if you were -- if you were the lawyer on that side, I took the stand.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "No, I remember it quite well.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "Do you remember the night that she died well, or is it now something you've blocked out of your head?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "I'm interested in what happened.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "Where are you going?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "Let me help you.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "What the hell are you doing?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "-- on your story.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "Now you want to know what happened that night?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "I'm curious about --", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "So far.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "Am I right so far?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "So I'm factually correct?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "I think you're here because you've written a book about your life.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "No, but your questions are boring, because I mean even what you just said, are you sure the people at Tibet give a (EXPLETIVE DELETED) about any of this?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "I didn't murder my wife.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "Than the murder of your wife?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "Because it's stupid.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "I didn't say you killed her.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 617, "question": "What the (EXPLETIVE DELETED) is the matter with you?", "qSentId": 616}, {"answer": "I said that you were acquitted in the court case but you were then --", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "Why don't you ask me some really interesting questions?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "I'm curious about how you deal with the fact that a civil action was successfully brought against you for killing your wife.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "You are curious about why I was found liable?", "qSentId": 631}, {"answer": "Yes, it is.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 645, "question": "Is it?", "qSentId": 644}, {"answer": "It's not so much factually inaccurate.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 662, "question": "What have I said to you that's factually inaccurate?", "qSentId": 661}, {"answer": "What -- that's another matter, Charlie.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 667, "question": "Hasn't it ruined your life?", "qSentId": 666}, {"answer": "We're not talking about how my life was ruined.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 669, "question": "Does it -- is that boring, the fact that this incident ruined your life?", "qSentId": 668}, {"answer": "I've said nothing about you.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 673, "question": "Don't you feel at all silly?", "qSentId": 672}, {"answer": "It's not what I've been able to find out since that night.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 689, "question": "With all that you've been able to find out since that night, who do you think killed Bonnie?", "qSentId": 688}, {"answer": "You can't go through your life feeling like this, surely.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 710, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 709}, {"answer": "I don't have any Hollywood friends.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 741, "question": "Which of your Hollywood friends stood by you?", "qSentId": 740}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 744, "question": "No one at all?", "qSentId": 743}, {"answer": "I'm grateful to God that I lived long enough to find out that 98 percent of my personal life was (EXPLETIVE DELETED).", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 747, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 746}, {"answer": "I live in an apartment, I told you.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 760, "question": "Where do you live now?", "qSentId": 759}, {"answer": "Well, like I told you, I've been on the (EXPLETIVE DELETED) for quite a long time now.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 769, "question": "Do you have any women in your life?", "qSentId": 768}, {"answer": "Which was the relationship with an audience and acting.", "docId": "120711pmt", "aSentId": 788, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 787}]